DE ROTTERDAM (demo)

This is the demo version of the font called “De Rotterdam”* after this huge and super cool building. (see the story below)

Free for personal use only. For commercial use and/or full version please visit:

store.rolandhuse.com 

or email me:

contact@rolandhuse.com


You MAY NOT sell my fonts or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename my fonts.

You MAY redistribute my fonts if:
1. You credit me (Roland Huse).
2. Keep the READ ME file intact within the zip folder.
3. Provide a link back to my website (www.rolandhuse.com).

Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

Follow my work on instagram @rolandhusedesign

Poster artwork background image by @reginar from unsplash https://unsplash.com/@reginar

This complex is located in the Top Van Zuid district of Rotterdam, on Wilhelminapier. I was lucky to see this building from the beginning (2009) growing up (2013) That time when I was working and living here. I was always amazed by the design and how huge it is every time I took a look at it while driving or walking on the Erasmus Bridge. When I was going to work or just hiking around the city. It has a special meaning and message for me: I started creating fonts in my free time in 2010 when I came to this city to work. I was factory worker, dishwasher etc. I grew together with this amazing construction from brick to brick, step by step. By the time its construction finished, I was able to quit my day job and transition into full time designer. 